SAHIL POONIA

2 sholebroke mount, Leeds, United Kingdom LS7 ◆ pooniawork99@gmail.com

Nationality: Indian

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Organised Management Assistant accustomed to offering multi-faceted operational support. Coordinates complex schedules and oversees appointments and meeting rooms. Manages internal and external communications to foster timely responses. Flexible Customer Assistant with professional experience delivering outstanding service within high-volume retail environment. Diligently processing deliveries, maintaining optimum stock levels and ensuring exceptional customer care at all times. Skilled care provider assisting elderly, convalescents, or persons with disabilities with daily living activities in-home or within care facility. Keep house by making beds, doing laundry, washing dishes and preparing meals. Advise families and healthcare team regarding health concerns, nutrition, cleanliness and household activities.

WORK HISTORY

Management Assistant, 01/2023 - 08/2023

JioMart - Delhi

- · Prepared research and statistical reports, synthesising and disseminating information clearly and concisely.
- · Enhanced productivity by coordinating itineraries and scheduling appointments.
- · Reviewed expense reports and invoices to assist with monthly accounting processing.
- Scheduled performance evaluation processes to inform recruitment decision-making.

Customer Assistant, 05/2022 - 12/2022

Domino's Pizza - Chandigarh, India

- · Provided fast checkout service with high levels of customer care and transaction speed.
- · Offered advice on product selection for enhanced levels of support and service.
- · Maintained sales floor stock levels through consistent monitoring and regular replenishments.
- · Performed daily opening and closing functions and inventory management.

Hospitality Assistant, 01/2022 - 04/2022

JW Marriott Chandigarh - Chandigarh, India

- · Established and maintained cleaning schedules in line with food safety and hygiene regulations.
- · Facilitated smooth running of kitchen areas by effectively stocking ingredients and preparing equipment.
- Demonstrated exceptional levels of customer service to maintain five-star rating.
- Supported 2 chefs with back-of-house set up and food preparation.

Health Care Assistant, 01/2021 - 12/2021

Max Hospital - Chandigarh

- · Aided service users in everyday activities, such as washing and dressing, ensuring constant safety and effective care.
- Administered blood tests and blood pressure checks.
- · Vigilantly monitored changes in physical and mental health, reporting deterioration to senior carers for urgent attention.
- · Safely escorted patients during medical appointments and hospital visits.
- · Met with patients and families to discuss care plan adaptations, seeking continual improvement.
- · Ensured safe, secure living conditions for service users, reducing risk and enhancing quality of life.
- Maintained high levels of client satisfaction by providing tailored, personalised care that consistently met individual needs.

Home Care Assistant, 05/2020 - 12/2020

Self Employed - Hisar, India

- · Promoted comfort, dignity and respect by providing outstanding care assistance in toileting, bathing and personal hygiene.
- · Conducted care needs assessments, using findings to tailor high quality care plans toward individual client
- Encouraged participation in social activities, promoting positive socialisation and community inclusion.
- · Improved patient satisfaction ratings by providing faultless personal care.
- Assisted in daily personal care routines for improved patient wellbeing.
- Led monthly case reviews to evaluate client progress and plan for continuing services.

SKILLS

- · Training and development
- Event planning
- · Record-keeping and bookkeeping
- · Office management
- · Professional and mature
- · Digital expertise
- · Problem resolution
- Results-orientated

- · Health assessment and monitoring
- · Self-motivated
- · Team player
- · Lead management
- · Staff training and mentorship
- · Brand awareness and representation
- · Queue management
- · Restaurant catering

• Compassionate care giver

• Food hygiene protocol

EDUCATION -

Bachelor of Science: Biology, 08/2019 - 08/2022 Maharaja Ganga Singh University - India

- Member of Literature Society
- Awarded with a medal as the best student in the department of zoology.

Master of Science: Environmental Health, 09/2023 - Current

Leeds Beckett University - Leeds, LDS

• Member of Education Society.

 Languages English: Hindi: Fluent Fluent Punjabi: Urdu: Fluent Fluent

TERMS & CONDITIONS | PRIVACY POLICY | CONTACT US



© 2023, Bold Limited. All rights reserved.